Guide to the Sir George Hubert Wilkins Papers
The Ohio State University. Byrd Polar and Climate Research Center Archival Program.
- Series VIII: Newspaper Clippings, 1909-1987; 4 cubic feet
  - New York Times, May 13, 1962 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 37)
  - New York Times, June 5, 1934 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 38)
  - New York sun, April 20, 1934 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 39)
  - New York Times, April 20, 1934 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 40)
  - New York Sun, April 20, 1934 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 41)
  - New York Times, May 19, 1940 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 42)
  - New York Sun, May 2, 1939 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 43)
  - New York American, May 10, 1936 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 44)
  - Christian Science Monitor, Boston, March 9, 1937 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 45)
  - The Montrose Independent, September 7, 1961 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 46)
  - The Sydney Morning Herald, October 6, 1955 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 47)
  - New York Times Book Review, August 12, 1928 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 48)
  - Unidentified: "Ashes Rites at Pole", "Ashes Strewn at Pole", Undated (Box S-NB-1, Folder 49)
  - Daily Mirror, March 12, 1958 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 50)
  - Presentation Invitation Flyer, 1940-41 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 51)
  - New York Herald Tribune, November 30, 1958 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 52)
  - Letter from Susan M. McLabe, January 2, 1954 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 53)
  - LaCrosse Sunday Tribune, Wisconsin, January 3, 1954 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 54)
  - Fort Lee Traveller, Petersburg, Virgina, October 23, 1953 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 55)
  - The Sunday Star, Washington DC, November 10, 1946 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 56)
  - Color Drawing/Paint; Leslie Lane, 1955 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 57)
  - The Pioneer, Anchorage, February 8, 1957 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 58)
  - Washington Star Pictorial Magazine, March 28, 1954 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 59)
  - New York Times, October 30, 1957 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 60)
  - Billings Bazette, Montana, October 8, 1958 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 61)
  - Pencil Sketch, French Drummer, France, 1918 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 62)
  - Ye Olde Tabard Lane, University of Missouri Certificate, Undated (Box S-NB-1, Folder 63)
  - "Top of the World Club" seal and ribbon (in envelope), Undated (Box S-NB-1, Folder 64)
  - "Order of the Top of the World" Certificate, January 23, 1947 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 65)
  - Letter from P.W. Roberts RE: Above, March 24, 1947 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 66)
  - The Sun Herald: Sydney, Australia, February 9, 1958 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 67)
  - Charcoal Portrait of Wilkins Head; Uk Uuchmich, 1935 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 68)
  - Business Machines, New York, May 14, 1936 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 69)
  - Business Machines, New York, August 12, 1937 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 70)
  - Caribbean Breeze, Panama, January 8, 1954 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 71)
  - US Navy Operation "Deepfreeze" Map, September 1955 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 72)
  - The Register, Adelaide Australia, March 5, 1917 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 73)
  - New York Times, 1916 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 74)
  - The Daily Standard, December 20, 1914 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 75)
  - Daily..., London, February 23, 1916 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 76)
  - New York Times, October 30, 1915 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 77)
  - The Seattle Sun, September 17, 1916 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 78)
  - The Post-Intelligencer, September 17, 1916 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 79)
  - National Enquirer, March 30, 1958 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 80)
  - The Boston Sunday Globe, May 22, 1955 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 81)
  - Detroit Union League Club Membership Certificate, January 18, 1926 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 82)
  - Captain Sir Hubert Wilkins Brochure, Undated (Box S-NB-1, Folder 83)
  - Australian Women's Weekly Pictorial, September 17, 1938 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 84)
  - Domain of Neptunus Rex (Lady Wilkins), October 23, 1938 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 85)
  - Everyweek Magazine Page Release, October 10, 1936 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 86)
  - Ledger Syndicate release, Philadelphia, September 6, 1936 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 87)
  - "Explorer" Brochure, Undated (Box S-NB-1, Folder 88)
  - Smith's Weekly, Sydney, Australia, September 6, 1936 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 89)
  - The Sydney Mail, September 24, 1938 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 90)
  - (Title??)(2 pages), 1939 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 91)
  - News.Magazine Articles mounted on poster board, 1955 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 92)
  - Edmonton, Alberta, Undated (Box S-NB-1, Folder 93)
  - Schweizer Illuftrierte Beitung, Undated (Box S-NB-1, Folder 94)
  - Honolulu Star-Bulletin, August 22, 1938 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 95)
  - Unnamed - "Hope Lies in Moon for Arctic Rescue", Undated (Box S-NB-1, Folder 96)
  - Moscow Daily News, December 27, 1937 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 97)
  - Russian Newspaper, Undated (Box S-NB-1, Folder 98)
  - New York Journal American, February 26, 1956 (Box S-NB-1, Folder 99)
  - New York Times, June 8, 1931 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 1)
  - Pusan Map (Korea), 1950 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 2)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner Progress Edition, Alaska, November 10, 1954 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 3)
  - Fairbanks Daily News-Miner, Alaska: News, November 10, 1954 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 4)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Minerals and Other Resources, November 10, 1954 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 5)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Natural Gas and Petroleum, November 10, 1954 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 6)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Military Bases Develop, November 10, 1954 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 7)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Education Activities, November 10, 1954 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 8)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Many Tourist Attractions, November 10, 1954 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 9)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Transportation Forging Ahead, November 10, 1954 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 10)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Agriculture Future Bright, November 10, 1954 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 11)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Changes in Way of Living, November 10, 1954 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 12)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Fairbanks: Alaska's Hub City, November 10, 1954 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 13)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Looking Around Alaska, November 10, 1954 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 14)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Discover Alaska Edition:, November 20, 1957 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 15)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Discover Alaska Edition: News, November 20, 1957 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 16)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Discover Alaska Edition: Its Status Today, November 20, 1957 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 17)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Discover Alaska Edition: Vacationland, November 20, 1957 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 18)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Discover Alaska Edition: Northward Ho!, November 20, 1957 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 19)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Discover Alaska Edition: Highways and Byways, November 20, 1957 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 20)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Discover Alaska Edition: Great Outdoors, November 20, 1957 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 21)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Discover Alaska Edition: By Sea and Rail, November 20, 1957 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 22)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Discover Alaska Edition: By Air, November 20, 1957 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 23)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Discover Alaska Edition: American's Defense Frontier, November 20, 1957 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 24)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Discover Alaska Edition: Year Round Land of Thrills, November 20, 1957 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 25)
  - Fairbanks Daily News - Miner, Alaska: Discover Alaska Edition: The Future State, November 20, 1957 (Box S-NB-2, Folder 26)
  - Book jacket Cover: Sir Hubert Wilkins: His World of Adventures, Lowell Thomas, Undated (Box S-NB-3, Folder 1)
- Series IX: Notable Individuals/Groups/Events/Topics, 1926-1971; 1.5 cubic feet
  This series contains correspondence and information concerning other polar explorers,significant individuals who had a major impact on Wilkins' career and life, significant groups and organizations that Wilkins was affiliated with, and major events and topics concerning Wilkins and his work. 1926-1971.
  - Aircraft: Lockheed Vega-2 Planes: ca. 1930's; Wellesley: undated, 1930s and undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - "Alaska as Japanese Colony Called War Solution": Statement by Sir Hubert Wilkins, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - American Antarctic Association: Proposed expedition for, 1954-1957 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - American Meteorological Society, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Bill: To authorize an Annual Appropriation to Aid the Arctic Institute of North America in its Scientific research activities in North American Arctic Areas, ca. 1951 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: By-Laws and Constitution, 1946-1954 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Correspondence, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Correspondence, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Correspondence, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Financial Reports, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Handbooks and brochures, 1940s-1950s (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Membership (and Fellows), 1948-1956 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Minutes of Meetings, 1947-1951 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    Primarily The Board of Governors
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Newsletter, 1946, 1948, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Notes: ca 1940's (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Printed Material: Grants in Aid: McGill Summer School, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Reports, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
    includes Committee on Membership and Publication, Ways and Means of Raising Funds
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Reports: Research and Fellowship Committee, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Reports: Bibliography and Roster Projects, 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - The Arctic Institute of North America: Stationary, blank letterhead, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Boston Museum of Science, 1944-1951 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Byrd, Admiral Richard E., 1926-1971 and undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Cook, Frederick A., 1940-1947 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Eielson, Carl Ben: Pilot of the Lockheed Vega on Arctic and Antarctic Flights 1928, undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Ellsworth, Lincoln, 1931, 1940-1943, 1951 and undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Explorers Club: Constitution: 1973-1974 Calendar and Undated, 1973-1974 and undated (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Explorers Club: Sir Hubert Wilkins Memorial Meeting, March - May 1964 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Human Geography of Australia: Course: For the University of Delaware - Sir Hubert Wilkins, Lecture, Summer 1955 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - LeBell,Clarence: Sir Hubert Wilkins Memorial Expedition, 1959-1962 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Mawson, Sir Douglas, 1929-1955 and undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - McGill University: Geography Summer School, 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Meyers, Ray: Lt Commander, USN: Member of Nautilus Crew 1931, 1977-1984 and undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Mystic Seaport, Connecticut: "Sir Hubert Wilkins Exhibit", 1959-1963 and undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Ronne, Finne: Antarctic Expedition: (Folder 1 of 2), 1946-1948 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Ronne, Finne: Antarctic Expedition: (Folder 2 of 2), 1948-1950 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Ross, Winston: Correspondence with Sir Hubert Wilkins, ca. 1950s (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Shackleton, Ernest, ca. 1901-1922 and undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Union: Includes a Report by Sir Hubert Wilkins, 1937-1951 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur, 1933-1962 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Thomas, Lowell: Author of Sir Hubert Wilkins: His World of Adventure, 1940s-1970s (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Series X: Notes and Reference Material: Non-Military, 1913-1958; 1 cubic foot
  This series contains material which is related to Wilkins' work but is difficult to classify into series. ca. 1913-1958.
  - Notes and Reference Material - Non-military, 1913-1958 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Notes and Reference Material - Non-military, 1913-1958 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Notes and Reference Material - Non-military, 1913-1958 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Notes and Reference Material - Non-military, 1913-1958 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Notes and Reference Material - Non-military, 1913-1958 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Notes and Reference Material - Non-military, 1913-1958 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Notes and Reference Material - Non-military, 1913-1958 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Notes and Reference Material - Non-military, 1913-1958 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Notes and Reference Material - Non-military, 1913-1958 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Notes and Reference Material - Non-military, 1913-1958 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Notes and Reference Material - Non-military: Vegetation Distribution in Alaska and Upper Canada, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Notes and Reference Material: Address Books, circa 1910, 1937 and undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Notes and Reference Material: Notebooks/Diaries, 1912 and undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Notes and Reference Material: Notebooks/Diaries, 1920 and December 1926 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Notes and Reference Material: Notebooks/Diaries, 1930, 1931, 1935 and 1938 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Notes and Reference Material: Notebooks/Diaries, 1943, 1946, 1947, and 1948 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Notes and Reference Material: Notebooks/Diaries, 1950, 1951, and 1952 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Notes and Reference Material: Notebooks/Diaries, 1953 and 1954 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Notes and Reference Material: Notebooks/Diaries, 1955 and 1965 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Notes and Reference Material: Notebooks/Diaries, 1957 and 1958 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Series XI: Photographs, 1908-1975; 8 cubic feet
  Arranged according to expeditions/trips,consultant work, Sir Hubert and Suzanne Wilkins, and other individuals. 1908-1975.
  - Balkan War, 1912 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Trinidad - West Indies, 1912-1913 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Canadian Arctic Expedition with Vilhjalmur Stefansson, 1913-1916 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    see also the catalogue by Stuart Jenness, Photographs and Films of the Canadian Arctic Expedition, 1913-1918.
  - Canadian Arctic Expedition with Vilhjalmur Stefansson, 1913-1916 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Canadian Arctic Expedition with Vilhjalmur Stefansson, 1913-1916 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - World War I, ca: 1917-1919 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    see also Box 52.
  - England to Australia Air Race, 1919 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Shackleton Antarctic Expedition, 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Shackleton Antarctic Expedition, 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Shackleton Antarctic Expedition, 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Shackleton Antarctic Expedition, 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Russia (Moscow), ca, 1923 or ca, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Australia, 1923-1925 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Australia, 1923-1925 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Australia: negatives, 1923-1925 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Wilkins-Detroit Arctic Expeditions, 1926-1928 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Wilkins-Detroit Arctic Expeditions, 1926-1928 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Wilkins-Detroit Arctic Expeditions, 1926-1928 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Wilkins-Hearst Antarctic Expedition, 1928-1930 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Photographs and Descriptions
  - Antarctica, ca. 1928-1937 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Graf Zeppelin, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Goodyear Airship Defender, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Ellsworth Antarctic Flight Expeditions, 1930s (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Ellsworth Antarctic Flight Expeditions, 1930s (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Ellsworth Antarctic Flight Expeditions, 1930s (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Wilkins-Ellsworth Trans Arctic Submarine Expedition, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    also called Nautilus
  - Wilkins-Ellsworth Trans Arctic Submarine Expedition, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Wilkins-Ellsworth Trans Arctic Submarine Expedition, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Wilkins-Ellsworth Trans Arctic Submarine Expedition, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    also called Nautilus. Descriptions of photographs.
  - Submarine Expedtion Photos, New York Herald Tribune, 1931 (Box OV-2, Folder 6)
  - Hindenburg, 1936 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Search Expedition, 1937-1938 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Far East, ca. 1941 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Military, ca. 1942-1958 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Military, ca. 1942-1958 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Military, 1942-1958 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Military, ca. 1942-1958 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Military, 1942-1958 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Military, ca. 1942-1958 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Military, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Military, 1956-1957 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Military, ca. 1956-1957 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Military: Royal Canadian Air Force, 1940s-1950s (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Military: Wilkins Arctic Test Chamber, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Military: Falls Cities Chapter - QMC Meeting, May 11, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - General: Alaska and Eskimos, ca, 1920s-1950s (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - General: Byrd, Richard E., undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - General: Calin, Ben, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Day, John, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - General: General Photographs (no theme), ca. 1910-1975 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - General: Polar Regions: Antarctica or Arctic, ca. 1913-1958 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - General: Polar Regions: Antarctica or Arctic, 1913-1958 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - General: Vesuvius Mountains, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Family of Sir George Hubert Wilkins, 1905 and undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Ford Exposition Honors Sir Hubert Wilkins, ca 1950s (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Individuals: Possible Acquaintances of Suzanne or Hubert Wilkins, ca. 1905-1975 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles Breakfast Club: Photographs and Newsletter, December 10, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Service at North Pole for Sir George Hubert Wilkins: USS Skate, March 17, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - North Pole: Flying Over the North Pole: Hubert Wilkins, Admiral Donald B. McMillan, Lowell Thomas, Colonel Bernt Balchen, and Lowell Thomas, Jr., 1957 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - University of Alaska: Honorary Degree for Sir George Hubert Wilkins, May 16, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - USS Skate: Sir Hubert Wilkins Aboard the Nuclear Submarine Skate, with CDR James Calvert, October 18, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Wilkins, Sir George Hubert, ca. 1908-1928 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Wilkins, Sir George Hubert, 1930-1958 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Wilkins, Sir George Hubert, ca. 1930-1958 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Wilkins, Sir George Hubert and Others, ca. 1930-1958 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Wilkins, Sir George Hubert, Capt Bernt Balchen and Walt Disney, September 28, 1932 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Wilkins, Sir George Hubert, Lincoln Ellsworth, and Sir Douglas Mawson, undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Wilkins, Sir George Hubert: Portraits, 1930s (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Wilkins, Sir George Hubert: Portraits, 1930s (Box 35, Folder 16)
    This folder now empty; all portraits of Sir Hubert Wilkins are in folder 15.
  - Wilkins, Sir George Hubert: Portraits, 1930s (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Negatives: Wilkins, Sir George Hubert, Suzanne, and Others, 1929-1975 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Negatives: Wilkins, Sir George Hubert, Suzanne, and Others, 1929-1975 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Hubert and Suzanne Wilkins and Others, ca. 1929-1958 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Wilkins, Suzanne: Includes Suzanne Wilkins' Paintings and Sir Hubert Wilkins Exhibits, ca. 1929-1975 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Wilkins, Suzanne: Includes Suzanne Wilkins' Paintings and Sir Hubert Wilkins Exhibits, ca. 1929-1975 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Ellsworth Antarctic Flight Expeditions, 1930s (Box 36, Folder 1)
    photograph albums
  - Ellsworth Antarctic Flight Expeditions, 1930s (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Ellsworth Antarctic Flight Expeditions, 1930s (Box 36, Folder 3)
    Photograph Albums
  - Shackleton Antarctic Expedition, 1921-1922 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Shackleton Antarctic Expedition, 1921-1922 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Shackleton Antarctic Expedition, 1921-1922 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Shackleton Antarctic Expedition, 1921-1922 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Group 1 - Instructional, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    all of box 37 scanned in printed in December 2003. All saved to group drive for Wilkins image collection, as well as in Box 2, Archival Masters, location 054-722.8-6.
    Box 37 originals include lantern slides, slides, some negatives, and some nitrate film, covering a variety of topics, including expeditions and military consultant work. All originals reside in Box 37, location 127-29-4.
  - Group 2 - Nautilus, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Group 3 - Shackleton, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Group 4 - Wilkins slides 2.2 x 5, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Group 5 - Wilkins slides 2 x 3, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Group 6 - Wilkins 3.5 x 5.7, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Group 7 - Wilkins 4 x 5, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Group 8 - Wilkins 4 x 5, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Group 9 - Wilkins 35mm, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Group 10 - Wilkins miscellaneous, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Group 11 - Zeppelin, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Second Submarine Expedition, ca. 1937 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Photograph Descriptions, ca. 1916 - 1940 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Photograph Descriptions: Ellsworth Trans-Antarctic Flight Expeditions, ca. 1932-1939 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Photograph Descriptions: World War I, ca. 1917-1919 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - 1954, 17 slides (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Alaska, 1952; 26 slides (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Alaska, 1957; 14 slides (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Alaska, April 1957; 19 slides (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Alaskan man, 1955; 19 slides (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Alaskan Maneuvers, 1956; 9 slides (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Alaskan Maneuvers, Moose Horn, 1957; 16 slides (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Antarctica, 1957; 16 slides (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Arctic Alaska, 1954; 18 slides (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Arctic (poor), 1954; 4 slides (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Bering Straits, 1954; 9 slides (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Cairo, undated; 9 slides (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Iraq, 1952; 15 slides (color) (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Desert, undated; 26 slides (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Desert, undated; 22 slides (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Desert, 1953; 16 slides (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Desert, Syria, 1952; 2 slides (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Duas, undated; 22 slides (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Desert Operations, undated; 12 slides (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Eureka, undated; 8 slides (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Greenland, Flower Stations, 1953; 30 slides (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Greenland, weather bureau, undated; 17 slides (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Lebanon, 1952; 7 slides (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Libya, 1952; 12 slides (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Libya, desert, 1952; 17 slides (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Marble Canyon, desert operations, undated; 26 slides (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - untitled, March, 1957; 20 slides (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Middle East, undated; 17 slides (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - N. Pole Flt., 1953; 23 slides (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Pakistan, 1955; 18 slides (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Panama, 1953; 16 slides (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Panama, 1954; 19 slides (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Saudi Arabia, desert, 1952; 22 slides (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Snow Surface Types, Point Barrow, Alaska, March, 1957; 14 slides (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Soil Samples, 1953; 14 slides (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - University of Delaware, 1953; 19 slides (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous, 1954; 20 slides (Box 38, Folder 41)